On this particular manikin, I would not recommend pulling her through a cap.
Like let's say this was my head, I would be very upset if someone tried to put a cap on me and pull me through, because that means this strand of hair to come through this hole all the way.
And you tend to get spots, because as you're pulling on that cap, it's becoming looser on your head, so you tend to get spots.
If you've got super short hair, the cap's the way to go.
But for longer hair, I highly recommend using a brush and a bowl.
And you can just section your hair off, grab some hair, and you can use foil, wax paper, you could even just paint it on.
And you take your product and you just paint it on the hair.
Now, let's say you don't have foil, you could take a piece of cotton, and just lay it underneath so that way it stays off the hair underneath it and let it just process naturally.
Another technique you can use on longer hair is the good old fashion mascara wand.
You just dip that into your product and you just paint it on where you want it.
A lot of times it's great to use in the bang area or around your face, and you just grab out that piece of hair, take the product, begin where you want, and just bring it back down.
Just remember that around the midshaft of the hair you're going to want to dip the wand back in and reapply.
Because otherwise you're going to get a really bright spot here, and not so bright here, and it won't look very natural.
Now a days a lot of the highlights are starting to get away from looking natural, so you can get away with that.
Another thing that you can consider doing is not so much lightening so close to the scalp.
Try starting just at the ends and just ending, just getting your tips light, or having it look like it's just grown out highlights from the summer.
So all you have to do is just take your mascara wand and just paint it on wherever you want it, and then let it process.
And that's one technique for long hair.
Short hair, like I said, you would want to put the cap on the head and then use your hook and just pull the hair through.
And those are a couple of techniques that you can use for different lengths of hair.